Most homes have a backyard. This home
>> [music]
>> has a destination. Today, we're touring
a home in Georgetown, Texas, where the
backyard alone might be enough to make
you want to move in.
>> [music]
>> From its incredible outdoor garden space
to its premium upgrades [music]
throughout, this home offers so much
more than you might expect at $448,000.
Let's go take a look.
If you've been looking for a home that's
move-in ready, but still offers [music]
those big-ticket upgrades buyers are
always hoping for, you're going to want
to see this one.
>> [music]
>> Today, we're touring a beautiful
three-bedroom, two-and-a-half-bath home
with a dedicated office, over 2,100
square feet, [music] and one of my
favorite backyards I've seen this year.
From the whole-home generator and
motorized shades [music] to the
incredible garden space and community
amenities, this home offers a lifestyle
that's hard to find [music] at this
price point.
How incredibly inviting [music]
is this living space? I absolutely love
all of the natural light, [music]
especially these large windows that
highlight that beautiful outdoor garden.
The owners of this home also installed
some fabulous motorized shades in both
the dining room and the [music] living
space.
Some other highlights that I think are
noteworthy are going to be the ceramic
wood-like [music] tile, this stunning
granite countertop, the stainless steel
appliances, double ovens, [music]
and a frequent request from a lot of my
relocating buyers is [music] going to be
this gas stove.
The primary [music] suite is beautiful
and functional with its vaulted
ceilings, spacious layout, and dual
closets. It's the kind of room that
feels open, bright, [music] and separate
from the rest of the home, giving you a
private space to unwind at the end of
the day. And how cute is this little bay
window?
Whether you enjoy gardening, [music]
entertaining, or simply spending time
outdoors, this backyard is incredible.
[music]
In fact, this backyard has been
meticulously cared for, and gardens like
this are getting harder and harder to
find, especially with new construction.
And no garden would be complete without
a vegetable [music] garden, and this one
has it. It has corn, zucchini, tomato,
bell pepper, and squash.
Another [music] major value add is the
whole home generator. The sellers
invested approximately $17,000
into the system, giving you peace of
mind during storms or [music] power
outages. Combined with the tankless
water heater and natural gas utilities,
this home offers both comfort and
efficiency.
Beyond the home itself, you'll enjoy
access [music] to an amazing community
pool, fitness center, playground, and
community center.
If you'd like a private tour, have
questions, or are planning a move to
Central Texas, give me a call, [music]
send me a text, or shoot me an email.
I'd love to help you make your next
move.
Thanks so much for joining me on this
tour today of this fabulous Georgetown,
Texas home. And don't forget [music] to
like, subscribe, and click the bell
notification so that you can stay
up-to-date on all things real estate
here in Central Texas. [music] Till next
time.